I'm building a brand, a personal brand, in the SEO and the AUO space.
I would do about 20 billion in revenue.
If you were in my shoes, how would you stand out at a crowded market when building a personal
brand?
What is the objective of the brand?
Get on more stages and to be able to speak more and to therefore get more clients.
Just make content about the stuff that the type of people that you want to attract make.
Disregard views, likes, whatever.
If you just double down on what is the absolute highest value per second that you can make
for that audience, you will do great.
The core meat of what you make should be as focused as possible on the thing that the
people who are buying your stuff want.
Even though I talk about philosophy, it's like, well, I had to understand how to get
through hard times so they could continue to do business.
I had to understand how to work with my partner, who's my wife, as it relates to business.
Most of everything is still through that lens.
Would you do that again starting from scratch?
Yeah, I would do exactly what I said.